<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Citizen Labs</title>
    <link>http://something-fresh.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Citizen Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://something-fresh.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/about/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/about/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Respect Citizen Labs is an intentionally positive community: that recognizes and celebrates creativity; collaboration of independent creators (and independence); and the diversity of people, cultures, and opinions that are a core strength of Citizen Labs.

Citizen Labs spaces are an inclusive environment, based on treating all individuals respectfully, regardless of gender identity, sexual orientation, age, disability, medical conditions, nationality, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), physical appearance, or technology preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/join/</guid>
      <description>What We Do We ask questions. We experiment and sometimes fail, but understand that learning cannot happen without failure. We apply what we learn and work to always make improvements.

We come together in-person to share successes, seek support, and work on individual and group projects. When we are not together in-person, we work together online. Citizen Labs has a Code of Conduct that applies to all of our activities, events, and digital forums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Team</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/about/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/about/team/</guid>
      <description>We are an all-volunteer organization. Our Board helps coordinate and set priorities for Citizen Labs efforts.
 Chair: Allen Clark Vice Chair: Brandon Klotz Treasurer: Joel Anderson Secretary: Max Dillivan Jace Browning Traci Montgomery Lee Mueller Sarah Titus   Interested in joining the team? Learn about the ways you can help, and then let us know.

Below are some specific needs we have:

Policy Guide: Work with communities and local governments on the goals of transparency, open data, empowerment, and community engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Work</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/our_work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/our_work/</guid>
      <description>How We Do It We use modern tools and practices to improve how decisions are made and services delivered. When working on projects we use the following guidelines:
 Design with users, not for them Invite participation and work in the open Use data to drive decisions Start small and continuously improve   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/about/sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/about/sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all of our sponsors who make our work possible through their important contributions to Citizen Labs.
 Adobe Airtable Amazon Web Services Bugsnag Data.World The Factory Google Heroku Hootsuite Intuit Mailchimp Meetup Microsoft Peppino&#39;s Slack   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>